

NHIVU

Portfolio: http://nhivu.com
07415 739224

vuvannhi@gmail.com

A combination of an engineering mindset and a creative problem-solving approach to create designs and experiences that people love to use. Analytical, curious and obsessive attention over details defines me. I am backed by a strong academic background with Master In Art & Design and by hands-on experience with a diploma in Web Design Specialist. I am competent in all aspects of the design processes.

EDUCATION

MA in Design Sheffield Hallam University 2016 - 2018

Diploma in Web Design Specialist Pitman Training 2013 - 2015

Certificate in Design and Craft FashionMallow College of Design 2013 -2015

BA French Literature and Civilisation 2002 - 2007 HB University, Vietnam

SKILLS

Low to High Fidelity Design & Prototyping Persona Story Boarding Wireframe, User Research Usability Testing

TOOLS

Principle / Marvel, Sketch/Figma/ Adobe XD, Photoshop/ Illustrator/ Indesign Bootstrap, CSS, HTML,

LANGUAGES

English French Vietnamese

EXPERIENCE

Digital Design - H&M Companies, UK, June 2018 to Present

Create and implement new design layouts; expand the e-commerce platforms with multi-sales channels; cross-platform digital design works; produce ideas and brand awareness for promotion and marketing graphics

Creative Design, Your Model Management, UK Jan 2018 to June (Contract)

Collaborated with developers created UI design for web applications; prototyping and front-end development for user-friendly sites.

MA Design - Sheffield Hallam University, UK 2016 to 2018

A blended course of study focusing on human-centred Design, Design Thinking, User Experience Research and making practices.

Web Design Specialist - Pitman Training, Republic of Ireland 2013 to 2015

Gained essential skills covering industry-standard software; implementing updates to UW's MHCl + D website.

Graphic Design, Freelance / Phu & Em Company, Vietnam 2013 - 2010

Working with clients on identity the visual requirements; develop graphics for product illustrations, logos, and websites.